I understand her hatred
The Fatui robbed her of the life she should have had
I never opposed her dancing
Yet still I became an enemy of her ballet
I'll just keep my distance
Many despise me
I'm used to it
You're certainly not one to shy away from confrontation
But children... they need a different approach
I'm hardly the most maternal figure...
Yet she is a child
In my experience
While a "Father" commands authority
He must still yield to love
You should tell her
What you think about her dancing
Odette will soon take the stage at the Korolevskiy Theater
This could be your chance
Geo Gnosis secured. It went smoothly
I'll be there
Have them send me an invitation
Sadly, things didn't work out
Her final words are inside that block of ice
This? Aren't these for monitoring her subordinates?
Not yours
This one isn't her "Witch's Flame"
But my "Two Worlds' Flames"
The "Two Worlds' Flames" can burn away memories
It was my parting gift to Rosalyne
If all goes to plan
She and I will both live to see the Tsaritsa succeed
I believe she'll find peace
But if anything happens to me
She needn't follow in my footsteps
The Cryo energy will fade away in time...
Then, the "Two Worlds' Flames" will burn away all memories of the Fatui
She'll be free to dance
She deserves this
I will handle the aftermath
The choice is yours, child